and have you listened to the news that the Russian
а вы слушали новости что а российские
military are saving Ukrainian people and
военные они спасают украинских людей
are trying to somehow improve this situation? And
пытаются как-то наладить эту ситуацию А
who are they
кого
saving?
спасают
Our forests and fields stretch from the southern seas to the Polar region.
раскинулись наши леса и поля одна ты на
You are the only one in the world. What a God-protected
свете одна ты Какая хранимая Богом
native
родная
land.
земля
Glory to
Славься
our
наше
free Fatherland of fraternal peoples.  Union of
свободное братских народов Союз
centuries-old
вековой
ancestors and
предками и
distant
Дальняя
wisdom of the people,
мудрость народная
glorify the country, we are proud of
слався страна мы гордимся
you Good day Hello Golo voice
тобой Добрый день Привет Голо голос
is good yes I am from Ukraine city
хороший да я из Украины город
Khmelnitsky And what city of Russia are you from Moscow
Хмельницкий А Вы из какого города России
Moscow Yes, I wonder if you
Москва Москва Да вот интересно это вы
sang the anthem of the Russian Federation yes yes And
пели гимн Российской Федерации да да А
why does it have such music  the
почему у него музыка такая как была у
Soviet Union had it, I was little in the
Советского Союза вот я был маленький в
Soviet Union, the same thing happened
Советском Союзе тоже то же самое было Ну
Well, it's a standard Russian gym, it hasn't
как бы это стандартный гим России он не
changed, no Where did this music
поменялся не А откуда музыка такая
come from?
взялась
Composed it Well,
сочинил
in short, we sang without music I don't
Да ну короче мы без музыки пели Я не
know where it came from, it's just a gym We sang
знаю откуда она просто это гин Мы пели
gym horoo Okay cool look eh You
гим хороо О'кей круто вот смотрите э Вы
specifically chose Ukraine Yes in chat
Украину специально выбирали Да в чат
roulette No no And I accidentally came across you
рулетке Нет нет А я вам случайно попался
yes yes We are from  Russia No, well I mean
да да Мы из России Да не ну имею в виду
that you didn't choose the interlocutor We
что собеседника вы выбирались не Мы
put all the countries just all the countries
поставили все страны просто все страны
Yes, but you have the Russian anthem on the blank, so is
Да но у вас на заготовке гимн России так
n't it you In short, we just sing Yes, no, we're not
не вы ли Короче просто Поём Да нет мы не
Katyusha We just sing We sing everything and you
Катюш Поём просто Поём всё и вы нам
came across to us at that moment  when we sang kin
попались в тот момент когда мы пели кин
a a what is the essence of this
а а в чём суть вот вашей этой
activity of yours You just want to sing
деятельности Вот вы просто хотим попеть
but just sing Well, we are in a
а просто попеть Да ну мы на студии
recording studio so you are some kind of singers
звукозаписи поэтому вы какие-то певицы
Okay, you just sing like that on
Да хорошо просто вы так ээ поёте
purpose look at my reaction see
специально смотрите мою реакцию видите
my flag No, we  not on purpose We're
мой флаг Да нет мы не специально Мы же
saying it again we looked at the text we
ещё раз говорим мы смотрели в текст мы
didn't see that you have a flag behind you and this is a
не видели что у вас сзади флаг а это
flag chuli Oh well Listen didn't see the flag
флаг чули Ой ну Слушайте не видели флаг
Well no need we really didn't see Did you see that
Ну не надо мы правда не видели Вы видели
we looked at the phone yes Okay I didn't
что мы смотрели телефон да О'кей я не
see that  We respect Ukraine, really.
видела это Мы уважаем Украину правда
Let's Maybe you
Давайте Может у вас перед тем как
feel
чуешь
fear in your
страш в твоих
Yala before you say it. I have something with Ukrainian, I
Яла у меня что-то с украински
have it maximum, not very well.
максимально есть не у вас очень хорошо У
You have some there, swear
вас есть некоторые там мати Ну то есть
words. Well, that is, there are swear words, for example, it is what is
там маты наприклад оно вот то что
Russian and  it is read as Ukrainian
русское и оно читается как украинское
so that is in most cases absolutely
так то есть в большинстве абсолютно
normal yes you And what other
нормально да у вас А какие ещё
Ukrainian songs do you know little in
украинские песни знаете мало на самом
fact I said that it
деле я то
is considered my own while I
считается сво пока
will tell you about everything so strong pictures tma
про все расскажу сно сильных картин тма
personalized with one hand so strong and lower
именными одною рукою так сильно и нижно
vai mene vidai meni flour their own  with
вай мене видай мени муку своими руками
my hands that me with my lips rejoice rejoice
моими что меня моими губами ликуй ликуй
yourself in the gray
себе по сед
on me you will scream because that will tear
на мене будешь кричати бо яже то порвати
and in the heart
и в серце сди
you feel How scary me at the shelves your Lado is
чуешь Як страшно ме у полок твои Ладо
dumb
нема
so acrylic so important rule PTA
так акрила так важно правите ПТА
ko understood Maybe you have some
ко понял Может у вас есть какие-то
questions for me  how do you live in Ukraine what do
вопросы ко мне как жите Украины что у
you usually eat in Ukraine usually eat Well
вас едят в Украине обычно обычно едят Ну
national dishes there And you like lard do
национальный блюда там А ты любишь сало
you mean what ordinary people eat or
вы имеете в виду что обычные едят или
what national dishes are there Well both this and
какие национальные блюда есть Ну и то и
that And you Do you like lard Well for example
то А у тебя Ты любишь сало Ну например
now yes I will answer Well well  borscht you know the
сейчас да Отвечу Вот ну борщ знаете
Ukrainian national
украинское национальное
dish there are for example
блюдо есть например
dumplings with cherries there are also
там вареники с вишнями есть тоже так
dumplings yes that is there are a lot of them
галушки есть да то есть очень много есть
with as for lard  we don't eat
таких с что касается Сала у нас не едят
it like that you know, but you know, like,
его прям так знае вот у вас как бы что
Ukrainians take lard there too They live but we
украинцы берут там и сало Живут но у нас
often have lard on the menu You know
в меню часто встречается сало Да знаете
what, I can tell you quickly I
что я можно расскажу быстренько Я в 7
was in a Ukrainian restaurant when I was 7 years old
лет была в украинском в украинской в
Yes, there was  very
украинском ресторане Да там был очень
tasty black bread with garlic and lard
вкусный хлеб чёрный с чесноком и Салом
it was divine and there was borscht I
это было божественно и там был борщ Я
also love lard but my mother overfed me
тоже люблю сало но мама меня перекормила
after that I somehow don't really
после этого я чего-то как-то не очень
like it that much
его люблю
look lard is not a
том что смотри сало - это не такой
product that you can eat in chunks  that
продукт что вот брать кусками есть то
is, when, for example, a sliced
есть когда например вот нарезанный
piece together with bread, for example, is served like this,
кусочек вместе с хлебом например так
yes and yes, yes, I ate it like this, but
подаётся да и да да я ел вот так вот но
I was still overfed somehow, no Well,
меня всё равно перекормили как-то не Ну
of course, if you eat it regularly, for example,
конечно если его регулярно есть например
there every day, lard, lard, salon lard,
там каждый день сало сало Сало салона е
I just used to adore it  lard I
я просто раньше обожала сало Я каждый
ate it every day it was incredibly tasty then
день его ела это безумно вкусно потом
something Yes after that not my mom
что-то Да после этого не у меня мама
always takes them on a hike only lard because
постоянно их в поход только сало потому
it is very filling Well, that's fat
что оно очень сытное Да ну это жир
Energy drink yes  it turns out Well, naturally,
Энергетик да получается Ну естественно
yes
да
So are there any other questions besides
Так что ещё есть какие-то вопросы кроме
Sala good topic Sala And let me
Сала хорошая тема Сала А давайте я Вас
ask you then look how you feel
тогда спрошу смотрите как вы относитесь
about the fact that Russia attacked Ukraine not
к тому что Россия напала на Украину не
really because it is a
очень на самом деле потому что это же
well-known fact that Ukraine and Russia
всем известный факт что Украину и Россию
so to speak, America quarreled, that is,
так сказать поссорила Америка то есть
all
всё вот
this, this all came from Europe and this is not at all a
это это пошло из Европы всё и это вообще
positive thing. I think that
не положительная фигня Я считаю что
Ukraine and Russia are to blame, but in
виновата укра и Россия но в большинстве
most cases, Russia is to blame
в большом случае виновата Россия потому
because Putin signed an agreement 8 years ago and did
что Путин 8 лет назад подписал договор и
not take Lugansk and Donetsk Donetsk  in
не взял Луганск ине Донецк Донецк в
their agreement it was just Crimea,
своём договоре как раз только Крым
so the war started and we won back
поэтому началась война и мы отвоевали
Crimea, on the contrary, Ukraine didn't want to give it
Крым наоборот Украина не хотела отдавать
to us. Well, in fact, Russia is wrong
нам Ну вообще по факту Россия не права
because in the agreement there was such a complete statement that
потому что там в договоре такой полный
no country would agree to this,
был типа никакая страна на это не
so of course no one
согласится поэтому конечно никто не
agreed. That's why in Russia  and they sent
согласился Поэтому в России а послали
these what's it called not not war
вот эти как называется не не война
but what's it called Now what
а как называется Сейчас что вообще это
was it a special operation on a special operation but
была спецоперация на спецоперация но
now it's not a special operation a
сейчас это не спецоперация уже началась
real war has already begun just with Ukraine and
реально война просто с Украиной и
Russia in short this is generally Dava
Россией вот короче это вообще Дава
let's do better Sing another song
давайте лучше Спойте ещё какую-то песню
on  Ukrainian language Yes, in short, we understood
на украинском языке Да короче мы поняли
that we are carrying the floor Yes, I understood it is better to sing
что мы несём пол Да я понял лучше спеть
Natalia, look, and my colleague, Victoria
Наталья вот смотри а коллегу а Виктория
Victoria My name is Andrey, look
Виктория Меня Андрей зовут смотрите
You said that America quarreled Ukraine and Russia
Вот вы сказали что Украину и Россию
That is, I am right I
поссорила Америка То есть я правильно
understand that America forced Putin to
Поня что Америка заставила Путина
attack Ukraine No, I  I didn't
напасть на Украину Нет я не
mean that I mean that
подразумевала это я имею в виду что
they know that America is a
они знаете такая что Америка - это такая
country that can manipulate
страна которая может манипулировать
people that is about it with
людьми то есть о она с
manipulation of the country wait Yes but it wasn't
манипулированию роной подождите Да но не
Ukraine that attacked Russia And Russia sent
Украина напала на Россию А Россия ввела
its troops into Ukraine because
свои войска в Украину потому что туда
specially trained people were sent there
заслали специально подготовленных людей
American In short, they acted on
американских Короче они действовали
orders from America And what And what did these people
приказу Америки А что А что эти люди по
do in Ukraine on orders from America, what did they
приказу Америки делали в Украине что они
do there I dont know Because I
там делали Я не знаю Потому что я в эту
didnt get involved in this topic, but I want to say that
тему не вливались но я хочу сказать что
America provoked all this
спровоцировала всё это Америка потому
because it needs territory because it has  they have a
что ей нужна территория потому что у них
huge population and they have for Ka what is the
огромное население и у них за Ка какое
population of
население
America Americans there well you say a
Америки американцы там ну вы говорите
huge population what What is the
огромное население какой Какое сколько
population of America I don't know what is
населения Америки Я не знаю какое
the population of America but their territory is
население Америки но территория у них
small because they built everything up with
маленькая потому что они всё застроили
their own  multi-storey building That is, you said
своми многоэтажка То есть вы вы сказали
that they have a huge population What is
что у них огромное население Какое
their population, I repeat again, I dont
население у них я ещё раз повторю я не
know there are about 250 million people
знаю там порядка 250 миллионов населения
there, in Russia The point is that they have
вот в россий Суть в том что у них
a lot of consumption, and Russia is a
большое потребление а Россия - это
huge territory that has a
огромная территория у которой очень
lot of resources  just like
много ресу ресурсов так же как и
fossils and non-fossils e once I understood
ископаемых и не ископаемы е раз я понял
in short a bunch of resources but Russia attacked
короче куча ресурсов но напала Россия на
Ukraine and not Ukraine with the Americans on
Украину а не Украина с американцами на
Russia And you and you listened to the news that the
Россию А вы а вы слушали новости что
Russian military they are saving
российские военные они спасают
Ukrainian people trying to somehow
украинских людей пытаются как-то
improve this situation who are they saving
наладить эту ситуацию кого спасают
Ukrainians  people you haven't heard
украинских людей вы не слышали
that
чтот
took in some there I don't remember at the plant
взя в какой-то там Я не помню на заводе
If you remember took va again again
Если вы помните взяли ва ещё раз ещё раз
again look
ещё раз смотри
again this is va va your TV
ещё раз это это ва ва ваш телевизор
was telling When Russia attacked
рассказывал Когда Россия напала на
Ukraine Yes me again look Here
Украину Да меня ещё раз смотри Вот
let's do this  already if we left before the
давайте это уже если мы отти до того как
troops went to Ukraine what is here who
войска пошли в Украину что тут кого
what hostages What Americans and what in
какие заложники Какие американцы а ч
general Girls you haven't watched
вообще Девчонки вы не смотрели
the news It seems to me Sorry this is
новости Мне кажется Извините это это у
me Do you know why Because I
меня А знаешь почему Потому что у меня
have a friend and  he has a brother he is fighting and
есть друг и у него есть брат он воюет и
he says they found a police lair where there are
он говорит они нашли логово полиции где
20,000 dollars and that is your friend is a
20.000 долларов а то есть ваш друг
looter No, just a friend knows Well, he
мародёр Да нет просто друг знает Ну он
personally does not do this well he knows that
этого лично не дела ну он знает что
Russian soldiers are looters I
русские солдаты мародёры я
understand stole 20,000 dollars Yes and
понял украли 20.000 долларов Да ещ
you are bragging not  you see she
хвастаются вы не понимаете она
said
сказа
to whom
до ком
it started Okay I see you are
это начала О'кей я я смотрю вы просто
just watching the news That is you are
вот смотрите новости То есть вы
informed such girls so but
осведомлённый такие девушки так а вот
tell me who is the head of the State Duma of the
скажите кто глава государственной Думы
Russian Federation what difference does it make what does it have to do with
Российской Федерации какая разница при
it please such a
чём тут это можно пожалуйста такой же
banal question no no Look look
банальный вопрос не не Смотрите смотрите
You just know the details in Ukraine that the
Вы просто знаете в Украине детали что
Americans are hostages, you know everything about Ukraine,
американцы заложники всё про Украину
but a simple question is that you have the
знаете но простой вопрос вот у вас
State Duma. This is the power of your
Государственная Дума Вот это власть ваши
deputies. Yes, who is the head of the State
депутаты Да Кто глава государственной
Duma of the Russian Federation? Well, can I ban
Думы роско Федерации Ну можно бана
the question for what is this? I
вопрос для чего это м я
understand, they poured it, you see. Yes, they looked at the phone.
Поня налили видите Да в телефон глянули
there is look you don't even
то есть смотрите вы без телефона даже не
know what's going on in your
знаете что у вас происходит в
country without a phone go do
стране иди
n't you think it's strange why the
вот вам не кажется странным почему вам в
news shows you everything about Ukraine but
новостях показывают всё про Украину но
something doesn't  they show about Russia they
что-то не показывают про Россию про
also tell everything about Russia Yes if
Россию тоже всё рассказывают Да сли про
we can tell you about Ukraine and about Russia we can
Украину мы и про Россию Вам можем
really tell you with no I asked I
рассказать реально с не я спросил я
asked about Russia Yes who is the head of your
спросил про Россию да кто у вас глава
State Duma and you don't know and
государственно Думы и вы оп не знаете и
that Putin is the head of state not the head of
что Путин глава государства не глава
state Putin Yes  you
государства Путин Да вы вот это вы
know this and who is the head of the State
знаете а кто уже глава государственной
Duma that is the body that is the head of the
Думы то есть органа который глава
State Duma we don't have a
государственной Думы у нас нету
State Duma we have it called the
Государственной Думы у нас называется
Verkhovna Rada well who is its head
Верховная Рада ну кто у вас ве её глава
Ruslan Stefanchuk ok and what next
Руслан стефанчук нчу хорошо И что дальше
I know nothing Well and you don't know  that is,
ничего я знаю Ну а вы не знаете то есть
I understand my country
я в своей стране
my question What if I don't
разбираюсь мо вопрос А что если я не
know what will happen to me for this Well, nothing
знаю что мне будет за это Ну ничего не
will happen I just wanted to watch I want
будет Я хотел просто смотрите Я хочу
you to understand why it
чтобы вы поняли что почему так
turns out that you know more about your own about a
получается что вы больше знаете про свою
foreign country than about your own Because  what is
про чужую страну чем про свою Потому что
most often said now about why
сейчас чаще всего говорят про а почему а
why that is why you are told more often about
почему Вот для чего вам говорят чаще про
Ukraine than about your own country And you know
Украину чем про свою страну А знаете
why I will tell you because so that you
почему я вам скажу потому что чтобы вы
do not ask your
не задавали своей
government unpleasant questions For example
власти неприятных вопросов Например
why do you not have a road why is the school not
почему у вас дороги нет почему школа не
built here  We have everything, we have everything
построе у нас есть у нас всё есть у нас
now, it's all being built Yes  look
сейчас всё это строится Да смотрите Вы
what city are you from Moscow Moscow yes oh
из какого города Москва Москва да о
Moscow maybe somehow more or less
Москва может ещё как-то там более-менее
normal life there Well you know Moscow region here
нормально жи Ну знаете подмосковьем вот
Moscow region let's take some
Подмосковье возьмём какие-то Химки
conditional Khimki so Khimki and we live jackpot I
условные так Химках и живём джекпот я
just know Khimki Pushkin and something else
просто знаю Химки Пушкина и что-то ещё
some  Sergiev pasat I know Yeah,
какое-то Сергиев пасат знаю Да ну
Sergiev Posad It's very far away there yeah
Сергиев Посад Это очень далеко там да
Far away yeah You see Khimki got there just
Далеко да Вот видите Химки попал как раз
in time look
во то смотрите
uh you were somewhere abroad Yeah yeah where In
ээ вы были где-то заграницей Да да где В
what
каких
countries Italy Greece Bulgaria Belgium
странах Италия Греция Болгария Бельгия
super yeah that's enough for me let's do that people
супер да мне достаточно давайте так люди
live in Italy  better than people in Khimki
в Италии живут лучше чем люди в химка
yes yes people are Greek people in Greece so I will say
да да люди гре люди в Греции так скажу
naturally it is Europe there everything
естественно это Европа там всё
is determined there are clear laws EU you f
обусловлено там законы чётки ЕС тебя ф
now Now look girls if it
тепер Теперь смотрите девушки если
turns out Russia is so rich it has
получается Россия такая богатая у неё
oil gas gold all these resources that
нефть газ золото все эти ресурсы которые
America wants to take away It seems
хочет забрать Америка Вроде так
so  all of Europe buys gas from Russia
то вся Европа покупает газ у России
pays money to Russia yes And how is it
платит деньги России да А как же так
that you poor countries without
получается что ти бедные страны без
resources also pay Russia and live
ресурсов ещё и платят России а живут
better than Russians  where does all the
лучше чем россияне куда уходят все
money go other rules in the country they are stricter
деньги другие правила в стране они более
and if you read the history of Russia Russia
и если почитать историю России Россия -
is a territory conquered honestly
это территория завоевала честным путём
conquered
отвоёванные
conquered and it is a business and without business
отвоевали и это бизнес и без бизнеса Там
no one can survive there Therefore
никто выжить не сможет Следовательно
If other countries buy gas from Russia
Если другие страны покупают газ у России
it is nothing it is not bad  I
это ничего это Это неплохо не я имею в
mean where the money is Look, let's take the
виду куда деньги Смотри вот возьмём
Czech Republic or Greece You've been to Greece
Чехия или Греция Вот вы были в Греции
Greece doesn't have its own gas there and that's it,
Греция не имеет своего газа там и всё
it buys gas from Russia, for example, a
она покупает например газ у России так
dog barks there and Russia pays
собачка там гавка да газ у России платит
money for gas Russia gets this
деньги России откуда-то она берёт эти
money from somewhere without  resources and Where does
деньги без ресурсов а Куда деваются эти
all this money go that comes to Russia
все деньги которые приходят в Россию
instead of you living Look look
вместо того чтобы вы жили Смотрите
And if the country has no resources
смотрите А если у страны нет ресурсов
And this does not mean well in short look they
А это не значит ну короче смотрите у них
have their own internal
же там есть своя внутренняя
trade we communicate serious topics and something
торговля мы общаемся серьёзной темы иже
adult Victoria please Yes Vika well
взросло Виктория пожалуйста Да Вика ну
please No no we are a very interesting
пожалуйста Не не мы очень интересный
conversation Look it's not often that we get to
разговор Смотри не часто получается
talk seriously usually people
поговорить серьёзно обычно там люди
swear there Now we are talking normally
ругаются Вот мы сейчас говорим нормально
we want to get into some issues Yes The
хотим забраться в некоторых вопросах Да
point is that every country has its own
Суть в том что в любой стране есть свой
business  Therefore, money also
бизнес Следовательно деньги там тоже
circulates there, they have their own businesses.
циркулируют там у них есть свои бизнесы
Therefore,
Следовательно деньги на то чтобы а
they have money to buy gas, and the money
покупать газ у них есть а те деньги
that comes to Russia
которые поступают в Россию они идут
also goes to the state for the education of
также на государственное на образование
children, since the state pays for our free
детей так как за наше бесплатное
education, and not a
образование государство платит и не
small amount of money.  taxes more taxes Yes no
малые деньги и налоги ещё налоги Да нет
taxes we pay ourselves Well yes this is
налоги мы платим сами Ну да это года
also for people's salaries also goes to the
также на зарплата людей идт также идт на
construction of roads pensions so right
строительство дорог пенси так правильно
look in Greece there is some kind of Trade and in
смотрите в Греции какая-то Торговля и в
Russia there is some kind of trade but Greece also
России какая-то торговля но ещё Греция
gives part of its money to Russia for gas
часть своих денег отдаёт России за газ
That is, Russia should have
То есть у России должно быть денег
more money if Russia has more money Why
больше если у России денег больше Почему
Wait, wait, Yes, here
Подожди подожди Да вот здесь
Thank you Can you repeat it again,
Спасибо Можете повторить ещё раз
look, in Greece there is some kind of Trade and in
смотрите в Греции какая-то Торговля и в
Russia there is some kind of trade Greece
России какая-то торговля ещё Греция
gives Russia part of its money for gas
часть своих денег отдаёт России за газ
That is,  Russia has more money How is it
То есть у России денег больше Как же так
that Russia has more money but
получается что у России денег больше но
lives worse than the people in Greece?
живёт Она хуже чем э люди в Греции
Because when the
Потому что когда был развал
USSR collapsed, our economy fell 10 times more than in
СССР Наша экономика упала раз в 10 чем в
Europe. Therefore, when the
Европе Следовательно Когда появилась
Russian Federation appeared, we began to
Российская Федерация мы начали
recover, but little by little, the
восстанавливаться но потихоньку ещё
war provoked something else.  more  the war provoked right up to
война спровоцировала че ещё война вплоть
here
спровоцировала вот
p the Second World War ended in the forty-
п Вторая мировая закончилась в соро
fifth year Well the point is that it was the
пятом году Ну Суть в том что это был
USSR and after the USSR collapsed
СССР и после того как СССР развалилась
our economy also fell wildly
Наша экономика тоже дико упала
Therefore our countries our country
Следовательно наши страны наша страна
it
она
me we'll take there Estonia Latvia Lithuania so
ме возьмём там Эстония Латвия Литва так
they were also in the USSR they  also
они тоже были в СССР они тоже
fell apart from the USSR So why do people in
развалились из СССР Так почему люди в
Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania live better than
Эстонии Латвии Литве живут лучше чем
people in Khimki And why do they live better? They are
люди в Химках А почему лучше Они же как
like I remember They, in my opinion, moved away from
как я помню Они же по-моему отошли от
Russia Well, they are now in Europe
России Ну они теперь в Европе
Therefore, Europe supplies them with everything,
Следовательно им поставляет всё Европа
all the technology, everything That's it  their
все технологии всё Вот это и у них
development is going much faster plus their
развитие идёт намного быстрее плюс у них
countries are smaller than the territory of Russia yes
страны меньше чем территория России да
yes but countries Smaller means they don't produce
да но страны Меньше значит не производят
less so that is to say they receive Well they
меньше так то есть получа Ну они-то
get a plus from Europe everything Yeah that is to say
получают плюс от Европы всё Угу то есть
Europe just feeds them for free No it's
Европа их просто так кормит бесплатно Да
not just like that  there is trade between
не просто так это идёт торговля между
them They sell one thing that is absolutely
ними Они продают одно то что абсолютно
that is they don't just give them money
то есть они же не просто им дают деньги
that is they also do something
так то есть они что-то тоже делают
sell that is yes and Why can't Russia
продают так да а Почему Россия не может
watch And Russia has Gas Oil coming from the depths in
смотреть А У России есть из недр идёт
huge streams all over Europe
Газ Нефть огромными потоками всей Европе
These billions are sold Where  what happens
Это миллиарды продают Куда девается
then what happens where does this money go all who
тогда что де девается деньги эти все кто
gives it to the development of Russia We are
их за го на на развитие России Мы
slowly developing We also
потихоньку развиваемся У нас тоже
have technologies Yes Why does he
появляются технологии Да Почему он так
talk like Russia is trash no no
говорит как будто Россия это мусор нене
again let's look at it again in
ещё раз смотрите давайте так ещё раз в
Russia money is coming in an order of magnitude More
России денег приходит на порядок Больше
yes  than in the same Estonia Czech Republic and so on
да чем в той же там Эстонии Чехии и так
No, well, look Sorry for
Да не ну смотрите Извините что вас
interrupting you now Russia is
перебиваю сейчас России деньги вообще
practically not receiving any money at all sanctions
практически не поставляются санкции
Americans were not the Americans but the
американцы вели санкции не американцы а
entire civilized world the entire
весь цивилизованный мир весь
civilized world Yes but before that
цивилизованный мир Да но до этого вот
look the Soviet Union has been gone for 30 years
смотрите 30 лет уже нету Советского
So  who is stopping Russia from getting out of
Союза Так кто мешает России вылезти из
this and living normally like other European countries
этой и жить как другие страны Европы
Well, probably society also doesn't
нормально Ну наверное общество тоже не
want to change everything the old generation of the USSR
всё хочет меняться старое поколение СССР
you know these elderly people
ское знаете вот эти люди пожилого
they also have a huge
возраста они тоже имеют огромное
significance for the country because there are
значение для страны потому что их тоже
quite a lot of them as What do you think,
достаточно много как Как вы считаете вот
look  I know, I watched an
смотрите Я знаю вот смотрел
investigation, you had a politician
расследование у вас был политик
Navalny who was now imprisoned
Навальный которого сейчас посадили так
for his policies so that he told everything honestly,
за его политику что он честно всё
he
рассказывал он
made a video that a huge palace was built for Putin in
делал видео что для Путина построили в
Gelendzhik Oh,
Геленджике огромнейший дворец такой О
by the way, yes  yes yes that is it turns out
кстати да это да да то есть получается
look it turns out that Putin instead
смотри выходит что Путин вместо того
of spending this money on a school or a
чтобы пустить эти деньги на там школу
music college or a
так музыкальное училище так студии
recording studio or something for talented youth
звукозаписи так для талантливой молодёжи
he spent it on a palace for himself for
он пустил на дворец для себя для
entertainment Well you know I don't think that
развлекаловка Ну знаете я не думаю что
this palace is just for entertainment
это дворец просто для развлекалки потому
because  security Tina is not a small thing but
что охрана Тина это немалая вещь но
I will also tell you that a
также я вам скажу что в нашу страну тоже
lot of money is also invested in our country and there are
вкладывается очень много денег и есть
people who spend their money and
люди которые тратят свои деньги и
a lot of money on more than Putin
немалые деньги на больше чем Путин
because
потому что
these are Putin's residences to some extent
это резиденции Путина какой-то степени
If you said people spend their money
Если вы сказали люди тратят свои деньги
For example  if you earned Here you are a
Например если вы заработали Вот вы
talented singer you earned money
талантливая певица вы заработали деньги
You bought yourself a summer house This is your money You
Вы купили себе дачу Это ваши деньги Вы
have the right to dispose of it like this And if
имеете право их распоряжаться так А если
for the state
за государст
there is money of all people including you they
есть деньги всех людей в том числе вас
built a
построили
palace and
дворец и
what e by the way Putin actually has his own
что е кстати Путина вообще-то есть свой
income are known for  state money he
доход известны за деньги государства он
did it either for money or maybe the
это сделал или за деньги или может быть
state got some money
у государства появились некоторые деньги
that Putin can invest in something for
которые Путин может вложить в что-то для
himself so that somewhere where is there such a thing in the
себя чтобы где-то где такое в
Constitution that the state if
Конституции есть что у государства если
some appear  money Their ruler
появляются какие-то деньги Их правитель
Wait if I'm sorry if you
Подожди если извини если логически
think logically if you
подумать если логически
think logically the Constitution does not say that
подумать в Конституции не написано что
Putin can spend state money
Путин может тратить деньги государства
Therefore he built himself this villa
Следовательно он построил себе эту виллу
something there I don't know You said with your own
что-то там не знаю Вы сказали на свои
money with state money since the
деньги на деньги государства раз в
Constitution says that he does not have  the
Конституции написано что он не имеет
rights of the state in the Constitution
права рати государст в Конституции
it is written that Putin, for example, cannot
написано что Путин например не может
take you, no, it is not written
взять ить вас нет не написан
here The fact is that officials can
вот Дело в том что чиновники могут
only do what is permitted by law,
делать только то что разрешено в законах
there is no
нету
such thing, don't look, Putin cannot do
такого не смотрите Путину нельзя делать
what is not prohibited in the Constitution, because he is
то что не запрещено в Конституции так он
like any other official  can only do
как и любой чиновник может делать только
what his powers are
то что ему полномочиями определено
specifically defined in the law he cannot take and
конкретно в законе он не может взять а
build a palace for himself nke because it is not
построить себе дворец нке потому что не
stated in the Constitution that it is impossible to build
сказано в Конституции нельзя строить У
We have a law that says that Neya
нас есть закон который говорит что Нея
Well, not that Putin is
Вот но не то что Путин
everything, but rightly there is a law that it is impossible for
все а правильно есть закон что нельзя
others  take money and spend it on
чужие деньги брать Да и тратить их на
your needs True Well you know the Russian
свои нужды Правда Ну знаете русский
people - They are people to some extent I
народ - Это народ в какой-то степени я
would even say more than 50% of our
бы даже сказала больше 50% нашего
population They are people and I will tell you so
населения Это народ и я вам так скажу
Putin may not be without sin and
Путин тоже может быть не без грешка и
investigators he may also be  build yourself
следователи он тоже может себе построить
a villa So maybe look maybe the problem
виллу Так может смотрите может проблема
is not  in America And the problem with Putin is that he
не в Америке А проблема в Путине что он
somehow imagines himself to be a tsar so-so and
что-то э возомнил себя царьков так себе
takes your money also so that
берёт ваши деньги ещё и для того чтобы
you do not ask unnecessary questions to him and his
вы не задавали лишних вопросов ему и его
entourage Oliry And do you know how much Putin
окружению олир А вы знаете сколько Путин
earns, how much he does not earn,
зарабатывает сколько он не зарабатывает
he has a lifelong pension  which
у него есть пожизненная пенсия которая
will be paid to him
ему выплачивать будет выплачиваться
after he leaves his post
после того как он покинет свой пост так
just like any American
же как и у любых американских
president I think I think that he
президентов я я думаю я думаю что ему
He will not be paid This is the first
Ему не будет выплачивать Это первое
Second I will tell you this chat roulette
Второе я вам так скажу чат рулетка
is bugged and if you
прослушивается и если вы будете плохо
speak badly about Putin good  ban
говорить про Путина гут забанить
seriously Well, let's say
серьёзно А ну давайте наче скажем
Putin,
Путин
you speak so aggressively right away,
говори вы так сразу
that is,
агрессивно то есть
you see, they understand that they live in a
бачите вони розумиють що вони живуть в в
repressive machine chatroulette if you
й репрессивный машине чатрулетка если
say something bad about Putin, they
что-то про Путина скажешь плохое тебя
can ban you, I
могут забанить
understand everything, but God forbid,
воны всё разумею но не дай бог не дай
God forbid, about the Tsar  something to say is not right that
Бог про царя что-то сказать не так то
is this is how you prepare to protect
есть це яки готови захищати
gnaws out she  the story that there is some
выгрызает вона разказ что там какое-то
generation of USSR grandmothers she herself is
поколение СССР ских бабушек вона Сама
so tall she is so
Така вона росте такою тобто Людина з
deformed people see
деформованим видчуття
somehow national dignity social
якось национальной гидности социальной
dignity so all the feudal lords offended him
гидности так все феодал его обидели
Europe and here and now Biden America
Европа и вот а вона вже байден Америка
provoked that it's just brutal
спровоцировала что жесть просто жесть
what a thing sadness in the heads of that  russia PS
Яка штука уны в головах тому росию ПС
that how Ukraine will win and when
того Як Украина переможе та Коли
russia split russia into an independent national
росию розли росия на незалеж Националь
state so it will be necessary to conduct not one
держави так треба буде проводити не одне
ten denazification in order to show how many
десяти денацификация для того щоб хува
people so special programs
людей так показувати специаль програми
drive x how they drove showed
водити х Як пом водили показували
concentration camps so Yes so Toto ma But le
концтабори так Да так Тото ма Бути ле
end of rethinking
покон переосмислення
the axis of the empire  taco husks Slava Ukray drink
ось импер тако шелухи Слава Укра пийте
put like obovyazkovo
ставте лайк обовязково
leave a comment if you
залишайте коментар якщо вас це вдео
like this video say so  so that we could see
зачепило вислови так щоб ми ВС бачили
also I have your thoughts if you think that it is
теж я у вас думки якщо вважаете що сть
correct to
правильна
trim a donation and subscribe to Telegram
трима донатом и подписуйтесь на Telegram
in the description of the video Slava
в опис п вдео Слава
Ukraina write on Telegram right now axis
Укра пись на й Telegram прямо зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg ORV your ban and very  I do
нас через скарг ОРВ твый бан и дуже
n't show a lot of videos to people sometimes I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim videos also interesting and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we will oblige you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
to keep constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in order to show you  about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter
пись а